{
    "basic": {
        "1": {
            "front": "QUESTION 1 SENTENCE",
            "back": "QUESTION 1 ANSWER"
        },
        "2": {
            "front": "QUESTION 2 SENTENCE",
            "back": "QUESTION 2 ANSWER"
        },
        "3": {
            "front": "QUESTION 3 SENTENCE",
            "back": "QUESTION 3 ANSWER"
        },
        "4": {
            "front": "QUESTION 4 SENTENCE",
            "back": "QUESTION 4 ANSWER"
        },
        "5": {
            "front": "QUESTION 5 SENTENCE",
            "back": "QUESTION 5 ANSWER"
        },
        "6": {
            "front": "QUESTION 6 SENTENCE",
            "back": "QUESTION 6 ANSWER"
        },
        "7": {
            "front": "QUESTION 7 SENTENCE",
            "back": "QUESTION 7 ANSWER"
        },
        "8": {
            "front": "QUESTION 8 SENTENCE",
            "back": "QUESTION 8 ANSWER"
        },
        "9": {
            "front": "QUESTION 9 SENTENCE",
            "back": "QUESTION 9 ANSWER"
        },
        "10": {
            "front": "QUESTION 10 SENTENCE",
            "back": "QUESTION 10 ANSWER"
        }
    }
}